

- +63-932-903-1580
- theysayflower03@gmail.com
- **Q** Cebu, Philippines 6017

EDUCATION

Senior High
University of Cebu Lapu-Lapu &
Mandaue
2016 - 2018

Junior High Cordova National High School 2012 - 2016

EXPERTISE

Listing & Contract Management
Transaction Coordination Support
Social Media Content Creation
Social Media Management
Lead Management & Nurturing
CRM Database Management
Email & Calendar Managementt
Client Communication Support

DAISY JAO

Real Estate Virtual Assistant

ABOUT ME

I support real estate professionals by managing the behind-the-scenes tasks so they can focus on growth, client relationships, and a healthy work-life balance. With almost 5 years of experience in listing management, contract coordination, and social media, I've learned that success in real estate takes both hustle and heart, and that's exactly what I bring to every task — along with reliability, efficiency, and genuine care.

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2024- Up to the Present
 Freelance
 Real Estate Virtual Assistant

April 2022 - March 2024 Your Virtual Sidekick | Cebu City, Philippines Real Estate Virtual Assistant

June 2021- January 2022 Maven Home Buyers- Justin Dillon | California, USA Real Estate Cold Caller

October 2020- April 2021

MediaFlow | Cebu City, Philippines

Chat Sales Agent

October 2019- March 2020 Sykes Inc. | Cebu City, Philippines Customer Service Associate- Technical

February 2018- June 2018 SSI Philippines Inc.l Lapu- Lapu City, Philippines Market Researcher

REFERENCES

Beverly Verano
Accounts & Project Manager

Phone: +63-945-149-8004 Email: ylreveb1987@gmail.com Jackie Sarabosing

HR & Finance Manager

Phone: +63-995-930-7223

Email: jackiesarabosing@gmail.com